In an impossible time, it takes impossible courage.
Bonhoeffer: Pastor. Spy. Assassin is a history, drama,
war film directed by Todd Komarnicki.
As the world teeters on the brink of annihilation, Dietrich Bonhoeffer joins a deadly plot to
assassinate Hitler, risking his faith and fate to save millions of Jews from genocide.
Dietrich Bonhoeffer, played by Jonas Dassler.
Young Dietrich Bonhoeffer, played by Phileas Heyblom.
Martin Niemoller, played by August Diehl.
Frank Fisher, played by David Jonsson.
Karl Bonhoeffer, played by Moritz Bleibtreu.
Paula Bonhoeffer, played by Nadine Heidenreich.
Bonhoeffer (released as Bonhoeffer: Pastor.
Assassin.) is a 2024 historical drama thriller film about the German theologian and anti-Nazi
dissident Dietrich Bonhoeffer, written, produced and directed by Todd Komarnicki.
It stars Jonas Dassler, August Diehl, David Jonsson, Flula
Borg, Moritz Bleibtreu, and Clarke Peters.
The film was released in the United States on November 22, 2024.
It attracted some controversy regarding political
interpretations and historical inaccuracies.
The film explores themes of assassin, spy,
pastor, pacifism, based on true story.
The tone is emotional.